ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Summary of Elections, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  January 1 - April 30th
- Elections. South, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Elections. New England, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Elections. Quin State, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Elections. New York, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Elections. Canada, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Elections. Mid-West, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Fact Power [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Fact Power [folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- ACTWU. General Office Financial Statements, 1977-1981 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Murray Finley, 1979-1983 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- FTR. FOUR. Misc., 1973-1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Four Grievance: Tate, Black, Pope and Jones, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Food Stamps, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Frontlash, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Fact Power [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Fact Power [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Union, 1967-1978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Joe Glazer, 1974-1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Art Gundershein, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Nabisco Brand, Inc., 1982 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Natick Mills, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  Natick, Mass
- National Felt Co., 1979 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  Easthamilton, Mass.
- National Mattress Co., 1981 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- National Service Industries, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Native Textiles, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Native Textiles, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- New England Carpet Co., 1980 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  Winooski, Vermont
- New Standard Dye and Finish, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  Newburgh, NY
- Nexus Industries, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  Culver, Ind.
- Niki-Lu Corp, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  Talladega, Ala
- Noramco, Inc, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  Athens, Georgia
- Nordson Corp., 1979 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Northeast Folding Box, Inc, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  New Bedford, Mass.
- Nordstrom, 1980-1983 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Nortek, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Norwell Mfg. Co., 1979 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Northwest Industries, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Norwich Mills, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  Norwich, New York
- Orchard Corp. of America, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  St. Louis, MO
- O'Sullivan Plastics, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  Lebanon, PA
- Owens - Corning Fiberglas, 1952-1982 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  Ashton, RI
- Owens Corning Fiberglas, 1968-1982 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corp., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  Hazleton, Pa.
- Owens-Illinois, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  Eden, N.C.
- PPG Industries, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Pacesetter, Inc, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Ortex Industries, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Packaging Systems Corp, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Packaging Unlimited, 1975-1977 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Pannil Knitting Co. ,Inc, 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  Martinsville, VA
- Papercorn, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Papercraft Corp., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Paramount Industries, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Parks Cramer, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Paulis Silk, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  Organizing Literature
- Pearson Yacht, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Peerless Rug, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Pedro, Carl and Sons, Inc, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  St. Paul, Minn.
- Pellon Corp., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  Lowell, Mass
- Pellon Corp., 1979-1982 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Pellon Corp, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Pennaco Hosiery, Inc, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Penn-Dale Industries, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Philadelphia Haircloth Company (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Pillowtext Corp, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Pittsfield Weaving Co., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Polymer Corp., 1976 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Pratt-Read Corp, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Preferred Plastics, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  Putnam, Conn.
- Purified Down Products Corp., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  Ridgefield, N.J.
- Rhode Island Area Targets, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Raybestos, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Readicut International Ltd, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Reeves Bros. ,Inc, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Reeves Bros, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Rennoc Corp., 1978 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  Vineland, NJ
- R. J. Reynolds Industries, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Rifkin, A. Co., 1980 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Riegel Textile, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Riegel Textile Corp., 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  Maryville, MO.
- Max Rittenbaum Inc, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Robin Rug Co., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  Bristol, R.I.
- Robert Samuel, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Robinson Thread, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Rochester Film Co., 1977 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Rohm and Haas Co., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Roselon Industries, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  Danville, PA
- Rospatch Corp., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Rubbermaid, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  Winchester,VA
- Russell Corp, 1977-1980 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  Alexander City, Alabama
- S. M. S. Textile Mills, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- St. Charles Furniture, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Sachville Mills, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  Wallingford, PA
- Salant Corp., 1980 (Box 39, Folder 52)
- Sampson Mfg. Co., 1977 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- Santee Print, 1954-1981 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  Charlotte, NC
- Santee Wool Combing, 1972-1978 (Box 39, Folder 55)
- Saratoga Knit, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 56)
- Sasser Electronic Company, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  Wytheville, VA
- Sasson Brothers Embroidery, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 58)
- Savoy Leather Mfg. Corp, 1977-1980 (Box 39, Folder 59)
- Schlegel, 1980-1982 (Box 39, Folder 60)
- Slater Screen Print, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  Pawtucket, RI
- Sleepwear, Inc, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  York, PA.
- Shalom Inc, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  Bristol, RI
- SherWoven Label, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 64)
- Schlegel Oklahoma, Inc., 1980 (Box 39, Folder 65)
- Scranton Corp., 1980 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  Scranton, PA.
- Sears, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 67)
- School House Candy Co., 1980 (Box 39, Folder 68)
- Siluria Textiles, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  Siluria, Alabama
- Somerset Knitting Mills Inc., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 70)
- Sonoco Products Co., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 71)
- Specialty Dyers, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 72)
- Spencer Gifts, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 73)
  Lakewood,NJ
- P and L Sportswear, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 74)
- Spray Textured Yarn, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 75)
- Spring Mills, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 76)
- Stamina Mills, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 77)
  Woonsocket, RI
- Spring City Knitting Co., 1977-1980 (Box 39, Folder 78)
  Spring City, PA
- Standard Coosa Thatcher, 1977-1982 (Box 39, Folder 79)
  Chattanooga,TN
- Standard Knitting Mills, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 80)
  Knoxville,TN
- Stanley Woolen Co., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 81)
  Uxbridge, Mass.
- Stanwood Mills, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 82)
  Slatington, PA
- Star Fibers, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 83)
  Edgefield, SC
- Star Paper Tube, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 84)
  Rock Hill, SC
- Star Porcelain Co., 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 85)
  Trenton, NJ
- Stauffer Corp, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 86)
  Anderson, SC
- Stearns and Foster, 1975-1981 (Box 39, Folder 87)
- Stearns Mfg. Co., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 88)
  St. Cloud, Minn
- Stedman Corp., 1976-1979 (Box 39, Folder 89)
  Ashboro, NC
- Stillwater, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 90)
- Storey Dyeing and Printing, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 91)
- Stylemaster, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 92)
  Norfolk, VA
- Summerfield Industries, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 93)
  Raeford, NC
- Sullivan, Paul Tennis Sportswear, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 94)
  Methuen, Mass.
- Schwartzenbach-Huber, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 95)
- Swift Textiles, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 96)
  Columbus, GA
- Synergistic Pigments of Mass, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 97)
  Fall River, Mass
- TRW., 1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  Belleville, Ontario
- Templon Spinning Mills, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Texagon Milla, Inc, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  Ridgefield, NJ
- Texapol, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Texberry Container, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  Houston, TX
- Texfi Industries, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Textprint, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  Japan
- Timex, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  Waterbury, Conn.
- Trend Industries, inc, 1974-1982 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  York,PA
- Trim-Tex, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  Williamsport, PA.
- Tubbs Cordage, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  Austin,TX
- Tulex Corp., 1980-1982 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  Martinsville,VA
- Union Underwear, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Uro Fabrics, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- U. S. Dye, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Uniroyal, 1970-1979 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Universal Textured Yarn, 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- U. S. High Pike Knitting (Box 40, Folder 18)
  Millburg, Mass.
- Value City, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Venture Carpets, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Vertipile, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  Leominister,Mass
- Vicoa, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Victor Balata, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Victor Electric, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Virginia Apparel, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Wall Fabrics, Inc, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Wall Rope Co., 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  Yarmouth, ME.
- Wamsutta/ Doblin Jacquard Fabrics, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Ware Mfg., 1980 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Waterbury Mattress, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  Putnam, Conn
- Wellman Industries, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Welpro, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Wembley Industries, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Werthan Industries, 1967-1981 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  Nashville, Tenn.
- West Coast Netting, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  Cucamonga, CA
- Westforth Mfg. Co., 1978 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Westover Knitting Mills, Inc, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  Indian Orchard, MA
- Westover Knitting Mills, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- West Point Pepperell, 1967-1978 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  Lindale, GA
- West Point Pepperell, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  New Braunfels, TX
- Woolworth, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- World Carpet, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  Dalton, GA
- Worcester Textile Co., 1981 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  Centerdale, RI
- Wm. E. Wright Co., 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Wright's Knitwear Corp., 1980 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  Hamburg, PA
- York Narrow Fabrics Co., 1980 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  York, PA
- Xerox, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Y. K.K., 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- ZRM Industries, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  Pottsville,PA
- Zwicker Knitting Mills, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Fred Whitaker Co, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  Roanoke, VA
- White Mountain Industries, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Winder Rug Mill, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  Winder, GA
- Wicket Ltd., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  Boston, Mass.
- Winona Knitting Mills, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 55)
- Wolverine Word Wide, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 56)
- ACTWU, 1977-1980 (Box 40, Folder 57)
- ACTWU, 1977-1980 (Box 40, Folder 58)
- PA Coord. Org. Project, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 59)
- ACTWU. Misc., 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 60)
- Progress Report. PA Organizing Project, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 61)
- PA Organizing Project, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 62)
- PA Organizing Project, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 63)
- Organizing Committee, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 64)
- Fred Goldberg, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 65)
- PA Organizing Project, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 66)
- Pennsylvania Organizing Project, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Staff Meeting. Pottsville, PA. April 28th
- ACWU, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Ohio Coor. Org. Project, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Meeting RE Co-ordinated Organizing Effort in Ohio, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  Cleveland Joint Board Office. September 12th
- ACWU Lehigh Valley, 1980-1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Allen, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Clark, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Franklin, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Holmes, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Miami, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Staff Development Project, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Organizing Information about Targets, 1974-1981 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Stark, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Warren, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Organizing Progress, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  Mid-Atlantic
- ACWU, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Mtg. -Committee on Organization., 1982 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  NY Headquarters. July 19-20th
- Greater New York Committee Mtg, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  May 18th. New York City
- NYC Coordinating Project, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Paul Swaity, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- ACWU Organizing Report for New England, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- New York Coordinated Organizing Meeting, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  New York City
- Potential Organizing Targets, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Organizing Gains, 1979-1981 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Draft Report of Committee on Organization to the General Offices, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Korea Int'l. Trade Union Conference on solidarity with the Workers and People of Korea, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- No Contracts. Elections and RWEs. Committee Students, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- ACTWU Organization Committee, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- ACTWU research, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Organizing Report, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Committee on Organization Reports to ACTWU Executive Board, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Meeting Committee on Organization, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  March 28th
- Committee on Organizing Meeting, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Mtg. Committee on Organization Int's Office, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  Board Room. October 25th
- Mtg/Committee on Organization, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  NYC. Aug.24-25th
- Committee on Organization Meeting, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Labor Board, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Organizing, 1979-1982 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Conference with Key Org. and Field Coordinators, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  Silver Spring, MD. Aug 17-18th
- T. Kenny, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- T. Misiaszek, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- J. Notarangelo, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- F. Nye and M. Pitt, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- P. Pope and L. Ray, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- J. Roberts and R. Ross & S. Sachen, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- R. Schnell and M. Shay & L. Smalley & J.E. Smith & H. White & J. Williams, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Off payroll. C. Addison, N. Bresciant, D. Haiglen, and D. Shook, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- J. Harrison and E. Sherman, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Canada. Clothing Division. R. Charland and W. Clarke, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- M. Robillard, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- J. P. Stevens, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  V. Catron, J. Cothran, V. Cumbee, L. Dorsey, and P. R. Downing
- R. Ernst, J Garza, J.R. Graham, H. Hales, E. Hamilton, and V. Hines, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- L. Agre, R. Archer, H. Bagwell, J. Ballinger, and J. Barry, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- B. Bozeman, C. Bullock, A. Brown, and M. Burris, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- R. W. Daniel, L. A. Dunigan, J. P. Mangan, R. Metcalf, and D. Rathke [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- R. W. Daniel, L. A. Dunigan, J. P. Mangan, R. Metcalf, and D. Rathke [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- L. Agre, J. Barry, and B. Bozeman, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- A. Brown, J. Craven, and P. R. Downing, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- B. Fox, J. Garcia, J. B. Graham, J. Heller, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- C. Jackson, F. Jones, and H. Jones, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Base Figures, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- ACTWU, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- ACTWU, 1974-1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- ACTWU, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens Educational Committee, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Bulletin Boards Ideas, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  Si Kahn
- Building Worker Loyalty and Support Ideas, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Organizing Dept., 1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens and EEOC program, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens Press Releases, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens Organizing Activities, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Letters to Stevens Staff, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- JPS Work Folder. Take up with McIver and Staff, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Employees Anti Union Committees, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Closing Hosiery Plant, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Corporate Pressure, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Stockholders Mtg., 1978 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- JPS. Straightening Things Out, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Response to What Company is Saying, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Contempt Ruling 2nd Circuit, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- JPS Contempt, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Company Attacks on the Boycott. U.S. Court of Appeals for the 2nd Circuit, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Speakers Bureau, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- J. P. S. Organizing Meeting, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Worker to Worker Program, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- JPS Staff Conference, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  Charlotte. April 18-21st
- Suggestions for JPS Workers Bulletin, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Staff Conference Agenda, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  Charlotte. April 18th Program
- Enforcement. NCRB Meeting, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- 5th Circuit Contempt, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Nationwide Injunction, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- J. P. Stevens. Re Black Issues, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- JPS. Senator Percy Statements, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- JPS. 5 individual supervisors, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- JPS Social Services Program, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- JPS. Organizing Staff Assigned, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 35)
- J. P. Stevens. Financial Reports to Stockholders, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 36)
- Plants where Substantial Union Interest Recently Reported, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Proposals for Leaflets, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Access, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 39)
- JPS. 2nd Circuit Court Contempt Adjudication, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 40)
- South. H. Bagwell, T. Baker, C. Farris, R. Freeman, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- E. Hamilton, E. Honeycutt, V. Keysen, P. Pope, and W. Smith, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- G. Krupnick, R. Manini, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- N. Bresciani, R. Harris, R. Esposito, T. Hummel, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- R. Mullins, J. Palladino, J. Roberts, M. Shay, and P. Stocco, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- R. Valetin, M. A. Wagner, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- G. Dion, J. Notarangelo, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- H. Bock and B. Fox, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- H. Boch and B. Fox, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Synthetics, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- R. Gray and J. Orange & P. Pope & L. Smalley, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Knit Products Plants, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Quin State. J. Manini and R. Mullins, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- M. Shay and J. Whitey, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- South. L. Agre and R. Archer & T. Baker & P. Downing, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- B. Fox and R. Freeman & V. Kesser & J. Orange & L. Smalley, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- ACTWU. D. Warren, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- New York, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- New England and New England Coordinators, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Off Payroll, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Quin State [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Quin State [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Activity Reports, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Canada [ folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Canada [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Weekly Organizing Activity Reports, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Mid-West and Upper South, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- J. P. Stevens [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- J. P. Stevens [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- ACTWU. Summary of Benefits. Misc., 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- J. P. Stevens [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Committee on Organization Mtg., 1981 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  New York City. June 15th
- Ideas for Improving Organizing, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Union Organizing Plan (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Meeting with Dian Nunes, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Coordinated Organizing Program, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  Cincinnati, Ohio
- Armour Handcrafts, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- New England Organizing Campaign, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- New England Coord. Org. Program, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- New England Program for Joint Board. March, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Organizing, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Organizing Committee, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Leaflets, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Shoe, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Blank Forms. Manufacturers List Registry, 1976-1980 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Sisters of St. Dorothy, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- National Organizing Comm. Mtg, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  April 24th. Washington D. C.
- AFL-CIO Org. Mtg., 1981 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  February 18-19th
- "Project Counter Attack" Conference, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  Washington D. C. November 13th
- Levi's, 198 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Unorganized Apparel Plants, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Ed Clarke, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Apparel Division Lists, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- New England Apparel Division, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Maine Organized Plants, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- New England Textile Division, 1975-1980 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated List of Major Plants Under Contract, 1971-1980 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Cluett Peabody. Continental Hosiery Mills), 1969-1978 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Apparel Division, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Apparel Industry, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Bag and Packaging, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Carpets and Rugs, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Coated Fabrics Industry, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Cotton Synthetic, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Dyeing and Finishing, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Fiber Glass Industry, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Headwear Division, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Hosiery Division, 1978-1980 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Knitting Division, 1977-1981 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Neckwear Division, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Non Woven Division, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Woolen and Worsted, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Plastic Industry, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Rope and Cordage Industry, 1978-1980 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Synthetic Division, 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Shoe Division, 1979-1982 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Monica Bourne, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Circulation Dept., 1981 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- COPE/ Legislative, 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Education Dept., 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Engineering Dept, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Finance Dept, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Jack Goldstein, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Labor Unity, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Legal Department, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- OSHA, 1980-1982 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Publicity, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Research Department, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Social Services Dept. Joyce Miller, 1980-1982 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- M and B Headwear Co., 1982 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  Richmond, VA
- Magda Pak, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  Phillipsburg, N. J.
- Magee Carpet, 1966-1971 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  Perry, GA.
- Malcolm Southern Spinning and Revonah Spinning, 1971-1977 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Marjac Mfg. Co., Inc, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  Brooklyn
- Masland, 1970-1980 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  Altmore, Ala
- McGraw Edison, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  Manchester, N. H.
- Metal Cladding, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Medline Industries, Inc., 1981 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  Detroit, Mich
- Mid American Mills (Division of Clinton Mills), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  Pryor, Oklahoma
- Mifflin County School District, 1970-1975 (Box 49, Folder 42)
- Millhiser Bag, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Millhiser Bag, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 44)
- Monroe Print (Franco), 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Monsanto, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  Bridgeview, Ill
- Monsey Products Co., 1979 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  Rockhill, SC
- Muscogee (Field Crest), 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 48)
- Muscogee Mills, 1966-1971 (Box 49, Folder 49)
- Muscogee Leaflets, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Nappe-Babcock Mfg. Co., 1978 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- National Spinning- Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- National Spinning Co., 1966-1981 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  1966-1981